Guide to the Harold Tokmakian papers, circa 1950-1990.
Tokmakian, Harold papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Harold Tokmakian papers, circa 1950-1990.
8620
Tokmakian, Harold.
9.5
Slides, correspondence, printed materials, reports, maps/charts, finacial records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection consists of professional papers, including city planning reports and presentations. Also includes teaching materials such as lecture notes and 35mm slides.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Harold Tokmakian was a city planner. Born in Sanger, California in 1927, he served in the United States Army in Japan just after World War II. After earning bachelor's and master's degrees in architecture at Stanford University and a master's degree in city and regional planning at Cornell University (1955), he worked as a planning consultant in Pennsylvania, drawing up plans for the urban design of Reading and working on several projects with Russell Van Nest Black. He returned to California in 1958, where he ran Fresno County's advanced planning division until he became Fresno County Planning Director in 1963. In 1968, he began teaching courses in urban planning through the University of California Extension and then became a professor at California State University, Fresno, where he established the department of Urban and Regional Planning. Beginning in 1970, he also served on both the Fresno City and County planning commissions. After retiring from teaching, he remained active in Fresno's development by volunteering as a member of the Downtown Fresno Coalition trying to save the Fulton Mall and through his work with the San Joaquin River Conservancy, working to establish the San Joaquin River Valley Parkway Trust. He died in 2016.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection consists of professional papers, including city planning reports and presentations. Also includes teaching materials such as lecture notes and 35mm slides.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tokmakian, Harold.
Subjects:
City planning.; Regional planning.
Places:
Fresno (Calif.) -- City planning.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. General files, 1927-2005
  - "A reconnaissance of southwest side of the san Joaquin valley, a need for long range planning", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Central Area Community Plan; Economic Development and Marketing, Fulton Mall District, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Concise History of the Cornell University College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Journal of the American Institute of Planners: Steinberg on the City, 1961-08 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Planning Group, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Little Table Mountain "on the edge', 1991-06 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - State Highway Route 41; Advisory Aesthetics, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Proposal for Development of a Comprehensive Water and Sewer Plan for Fresno County Board of Supervisors, 1970-06 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Development of a Feasibility Study for a Computerized Land Use System, 1972-12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - West side Freeway, General Plan, 1965-08-26 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Urban Physical Factors Phase 1, 1968-07 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Community Data Register Phase 2, 1969-06-22 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Interagency Planning for Urban Education Needs
  - 1970-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Russell VanNest Black, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Planning and Plan for Monticello, 1958-08 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Planning and Zoning for Monticello, 1958-08 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Zoning in the Central Berks Region, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Central Berks Regional Plan, 1958-10-1970-09 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Highway 1990 Classification
  - Planning and Zoning Ontelaunee Township, 1959-06 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Remarks to the Press, 1957-09 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Planning and Zoning for Emmaus, PA, 1957-05 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Cornell Kitchen, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - General Plan for Boston, 1950-12 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Master Plan for Morestown Township, NJ, 1956-12 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Principles City Planning; Notes, 1952-11-29-1953-01-20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Arch 700 History of City Planning; Notes, Spring 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Development of Paris; Term Paper, 1954-05-18 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Russell Van Nest Black Historic Publications, 1927-09-1944 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cowdrey Court - A Problem in Urban Land Appraisal; Term Paper, 1954-01-22 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - CP 240 Theories of Urban Form and Design, Spring 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Environmental Law CRP Cal. State, Fresno, 1992-01 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Guidelines for Hospital Mergers - Feasibility Studies, 1976-04 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Hospital District Consolidations
  - Home Health Agency Grant Application, 1979-03-01 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sanger Housing Study, 1976-05 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Pedestrian Environment of Downtown San Francisco and its Design, Fall 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    A Study of Regulatory Mechanisms and the Administrative Process
  - Teaching Notes UC Berkeley, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1980-1981 Sabbatical Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Volume 1 Timeline and Field Notes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Tax Deductions
  - Volume 2 Part 1 Timeline and Field Notes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Volume 2 Part 2 Timeline and Field Notes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Certificate APA Charter Member, 2003-10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Infill According to Principles of New Urbanism, 1999-11-22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Letter to a student from Lewis Mumford (copy), 1966-02-12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photos relating to Mountain View Infill, 1999-05-16 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Social Profile, Tulare County, 1978-10-09 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sierra National Forest Economic Base Study, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fresno County General Plan, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bullard Community General Plan, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Application and Proposal for Sabbatical Leave, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Travel Notes US 1989, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Travel Notes Europe 1990, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Field Notes, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Field Notes, 1990-2008 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Field Notes, 1982-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 1 Westside Valley Water and Sewer Plans, 1971 (Box 2)
    Fresno County Rural Communities
  - Vol. 2 Westside Valley Water and Sewer Plans, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Vol. 3 Westside Valley Water and Sewer Plans, 1971 (Box 2)
  - CRP Brochures Flyers, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Central Area Planning Task Force, 1986-04-08 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CRP 202 Misc. Course Material, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CRP 202 Master File and Handouts, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CRP 202 Notes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CRP 202 Notes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CRP 203A Notes, Spring 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Practicum in community planning
  - CRP 135 Transparencies, Fall 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CRP 203A Notes, Spring 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CRP 203A Notes, Spring 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CRP 203A Notes, Spring 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CRP 135 Class Handouts, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Downtown Malls Slide Presentation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Design Articles by Allan Temko, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CRP 135 Reader Env. Law Original, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - CRP 202 Reader Original, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 2 Part 1, Spring 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 2 Part 2, Spring 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 1 Part 1, Spring 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 1 Part 2, Spring 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 3 Part 1, Spring 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 3 Part 2, Spring 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CRP 202 Notes Vol. 3 Part 3, Spring 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.1 Part 1, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.1 Part 2, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.1 Part 3, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.2 Part 1, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.2 Part 2, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.3 Part 1, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CRP 135 Notes Vol.3 Part 2, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Site Planning Lecture Notes, 1986-09-09 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Series II. Slides, 1956-2005
  - Slides from places researched, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Slides from unlabeled binder, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Slides from unlabeled binder, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Slides from unlabeled binder, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A/B California Cities LA, San Diego, SF, Larkspur, Santa Barbara, Solvang, Disneyland, Foster City, etc, 1975-1984 (Box 5)
  - C. Foothill College, Sacramento, Berkeley, 1979-1985 (Box 5)
  - D. San Francisco Neighborhoods, 1982-1985 (Box 5)
  - E. Washington DC, Reston, Baltimore, Philadelphia, Annapolis, Williamsburg, Univ of VA, Pittsburgh, 1982-1987 (Box 5)
  - F. Toronto 1967, Quebec 1967, Habitat, New Hope/Reading, Cape Cod 1956, Radburnn, Minneapolis, 1956-1967 (Box 5)
  - G. Eugene, Seattle, Vancouver, 1981-1984 (Box 5)
  - H. New England Villages, Chicago, River Manufacturing Cities, 1981-1984 (Box 6)
  - I Philadelphia Rockefeller Center, New Haven, Boston, 1982 (Box 6)
  - J. Santa Cruz, UCSC, Asilomar, Pacific Grove, 1980-1985 (Box 6)
  - K. Rocky Mountain Cities, SW Native American, Spanish, 1983-1987 (Box 6)
  - L. Env. Planning Natural Resources, Sea Ranch, Village Homes, Reading, Eureka, Fresno, 1985-1990 (Box 6)
  - M. Portland, 1976-1988 (Box 6)
  - N. San Francisco, 1969-1985 (Box 6)
  - O. San Francisco, 1973-1985 (Box 7)
  - P. Rocky Mountains, Boise, SW Cities, Denver, 1982-1986 (Box 7)
  - Q. Toronto, Montreal, Quebec, 1984 (Box 7)
  - UK, Edinburgh, Rye, Cambridge, Bedford Pk, Bourneville, Cotswold Villages, 1979-1987 (Box 7)
  - London #1, 1975-1987 (Box 7)
  - London #2, Rome, York, Venice, 1985-1990 (Box 7)
  - Minneapolis, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Ottawa, Calgary, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Horton Plaza, Pullman, Boston, Philadelphia, Savannah, New Orleans, Washington DC Spring 1989, 1989Spring 1989 (Box 8)
  - Paris #1, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Paris Versaille #2, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Hampstead Garden Suburb, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Eureka, Irvine Center, Luna Fields, 1976-1980 (Box 8)
  - Photographs and negatives of Sun River Oregon, 1988Summer 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and negatives of Eugene Mall Oregon, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and negatives of San Diego, 1989-06 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Photographs and negatives of 3rd Street Promenade Santa Monica, 2002-05-13 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of P. Kennedy Projects Berkeley, 2003-03-03 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Vendor Cart Photos (Boulder, Denver, Santa Monica), 2003-04-2003-06 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 55/85 SF, Bass Lake (CA) landslide, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 56/85 Fresno Street Scenes, SJ River flooding, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1/86 Boise/San Joaquin River Flood, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2/86 SF. N. Beach, Presidio Bay, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 5/86 Greenbelt MD, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 7/86 Annapolis, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 8/86 Wash DC, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 8/86? Wash DC, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 10/86 Williamsburg VA, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 11/86 Williamsburg/ Richmond VA, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 12/86 Richmond VA, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 13/86 Richmond/Charlottesville VA, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 14/86 Monticello VA, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 15/86 Monticello VA / Dulles, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 16/86 Portland, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 17/86 Portland, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 18/86 Portland, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 19/86 Portland, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 20/86 Portland, Sisters, Boise, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 21/86 Boise, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 22/86 Halprin Show SF, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 23/86 SF, Berkeley, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 24/86 LA/Laguna, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 25/86 Laguna, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 26/86 Various CA, Napa, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 27/86 Napa, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 28/86 CA Wineries, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 29/86 Bulldog Village Fresno, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 30/86 Sacramento, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - American River Pkwy, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 87 Maps letchworth/London, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1/87 San Francisco, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2/87 Boise & Santa Monica, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 3/87 Fresno Farmers Market / Santa Cruz, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Letchworth Garden Cities, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Not taken by H. Tokmakian
  - 1/88 Eugene Mall, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2/88 Boise Downtown, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2/88 Boise Downtown, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 10/88 Ashland/Eugene, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 11/88 Eugene Downtown + Corvallis, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 12/88 Corvallis, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 13/88 Portland, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 14/88 Sacramento "K" st Mall, Somerset Parkside, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 15/88 Santa Cruz, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 4/89 New Orleans, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 5/89 New Orleans, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 11/89 Boston, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 12/89 Boston, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 13/89 Philadelphia, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 15/89 Boston, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 16/89 Boston, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 19/89 Boston, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 20/89 Boston, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 21/89 En route & chicago, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 22/89 Chicago, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 23/89 Chicago, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 24/89 Minneapolis, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 28/89 Enroute to Portland & Portland, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 29/89 Portland and enroute to SF, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 30/89 San Jose & Palo Alto, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 31/89 San Jose, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 32/89 Portland, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Santa Cruz Earthquake, 1989-11 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Santa Cruz Earthquake, 1989-11 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Santa Cruz Earthquake, 1989-11 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Palo Alto, 1989-12 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 2/90 Santa Cruz Pacific Garden Mall (Earthquake Remains), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 3/90 Marin Civic Center, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 4/90 Fresno City Hall Construction, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 5/90 Newport Fashion Island, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 6/90 London/Chichester, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 7/90 Chichester/London, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 8/90 Guildford/London, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 9/90 Milan?, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 10/90 Milan, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 11/90 Rome, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 12/90 Rome, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 13/90 Rome, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 14/90 Rome, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 15/90 Rome/Florence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 16/90 Florence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 17/90 Florence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 18/90 Florence/Siena, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 19/90 Siena/Pienza, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 20/90 Pienza/Siena, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 21/90 Siena/Sangimignano, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 22/90 San Gimignamo/Perugia, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 23/90 Perugia/Gubbio, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 24/90 Gubbio/Spoleto, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 25/90 Spoleto/Todi, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 26/90 Orvieto, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 27/90 Arrezo/Venice, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 28/90 Venice, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 29/90 Venice, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 30/90 Venice, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 31/90 Venice/Vienna, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 32/90 Vienna, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 33/90 Vienna, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 34/90 Prague, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 35/90 Prague, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 36/90 Prague, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 37/90 Enroute + Paris, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 38/90 Paris/La Defense, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 39/90 Paris, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 40/90 Paris/winchester/HGS, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 41/90 HGS, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1/91 Rural Fresno Hwy 41, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2/91 Rural Fresno, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 4/91 Portland, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 5/91 Portland, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 6/91 Portland, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 7/91 Portland, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 8/91 Portland/Eugene, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 9/91 London Docklands, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 10/91 Kew Gardens, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 11/91 Hampstead Garden Suburbs (HGS), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 12/91 London - Ruskin Close, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 14/91 London, Finchley, Rowley Way (mega council housing, terraced), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 15/91 Nash's Park Village West (UK), Kenwood House, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 16/91 Hampstead Garden Suburb, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 18/91 Cotswold Oxford #1, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 18/91 Cotswold #2, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 19/91 HGS, Oakwood Rd, Denmar Rd Oxford, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 20/91 London, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 21/91 London Royal Hospital, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 22/91 London Canary Wharf, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 23/91 Chiswick, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 24/91 Bourneville, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 25/91 HGS, Belgrave Sq, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 26/91 LondonBelgrave Sq, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1/92 Stanford Shopping Center, Mountain View City Hall & Park, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 2/92 U of O Eugene, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 3/92 Eugene, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 4/92 Eugene/Portland, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 6/92 Missoula, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 7/92 Seattle, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 35 Chartres, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 202/2 Defs/Concepts, 1980-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 202/3 Medieval Cities images/form British Pueblos, 1968-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 202/3 Sienna and Medieval Italian Hill Towns Umbria, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 202/4-1 Medieval Cities Cases 1 Milan Galeria Pompidou Centre, Nicollet Mall, 1981-1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 202/4-2 UCSC Kresge, Boston City Hall Mkts, Horton Plaza, 1980-1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 202/4-3 Medieval City - Cases: Harbor Place, Pikes Mkt, Kensington (UK), British Mkts, 1981-1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 202/4-4 Medieval City -Cases: Giradelli, Anchorage, Eaton Galleria, Paris Streets, SF City Hall, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 202/5-1 Baroque City, Venice, Alberti, Florence, Pienza, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 202/5-2 Baroque City, Campidoglio, Piazza del Popolo, Pizza Novona, Spanish Steps, St. Peters, 1968-1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 202/5-3 Baroque City Versaille, Champs Elysee,Louvre,Tuileries, 1968-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 202/6-1 Baroque City, Washington DC, 1968-1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 202/6-2 Baroque City, BK Parkway, SF Civic Center, Salk, 1969-1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 202-6-3 Colonial Cities New Haven, UVA, London Sq, Phla- Society Hill, Boston - Lou. Sq., 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 202/6-4 Colonial Cities Savan00nah Williamsburg, Santa Fe, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 202/8 Industrial/Western Cities R.R., 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 202/9-1 Garden Cities, Howorth, Bedworth Park, New Earwick, Greenbelt, 1968-1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 202/9-2 Garden Cities, Letchworth, Hampstead, Welivin (UK), 1985-1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 202/10-1 Garden Cities, Harlow, Reston, M-K., 1967-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 202/10-2 Village Homes, CA, 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 202/11-12 Machine City Corbu, Paris, LA Downtown, Domin.Bk., Brasilia, 1974-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 202/12 Machine City Cases, 1982-1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 202/13-1 Humane City, Covent Garden, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 202/13-2 Humane City, Portland Pioneer Sq, Portland Center, Santa Cruz Mall, 1980-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - 202/13-3 Humane City, Levis Pk, S Fremont, SF Downtown Plazas, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 202/13-4 Humane City, Urban Devel. Principles, Seattle Freeway Park, Portland, 1976-1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Docklands (London, UK), 1981-1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Chicago buildings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Getty Museum, 2002-05-22 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Breeze House. Meno Park CA, 2002-05-31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Portland, 2005-05-11 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Medium format slides - Santa Clara, 1962-12 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous souvenir slides, Date unknown (Box 13)